<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_NAME1]">Sable</Text>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0000]">I met with our contact again--</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0001]">I met with our contact again.  Seems the Alloy delivery went to their liking.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0002]">Wait a minute.  Before you continue, why is it that we always get notified we need to meet with their contact when we&apos;re in orbit of Serpens III but they always want us to meet them in Serpens Station?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0003]">Well it wasn&apos;t really that difficult.  They actually paid us a little too.  I didn&apos;t expect that.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0004]">Good question.  We&apos;ve been to his manor, we know where to find him personally.  It could be that his activities involving us aren&apos;t sanctioned by the rest of the MRI, and he can fly under the radar if we meet a contact at a busy hub like Serpens Station instead of meeting with him directly.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0005]">True, but it was necessary to prove we could get what we needed from our surroundings.  I suppose he thinks we&apos;ll need such a skill with our future testing out their technology.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0006]">Interesting.  That makes me wonder what our next task is going to be?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0007]">Alright then.  You met with the contact, what are we to do next?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0008]">Two more convicts have been released from their life imprisonment solely so we can find and destroy them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0009]">Two more convicts have been released from their life imprisonment solely so we can find and destroy them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0010]">Alright, have they been marked like the last one?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0011]">Is that even legal?  Isn&apos;t that trading their life sentences for death penalties?  Seems like an awful thing to do, even to a couple of convicts.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0012]">Yes, they should be somewhere in the Apus System according to our tracking device.  We need to find them before they discover and remove their signal beacons.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0013]">Well how do you think he earned the name, Nasty Butler?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0014]">Alright, anything special about these convicts I should know?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0015]">I thought you said there wasn&apos;t a story behind his name?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0016]">They were skilled pirates before they were captured, and that wasn&apos;t long ago.  You can expect them to be skilled Pilots and Gunners.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0017]">There isn&apos;t.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0018]">I&apos;ll keep that in mind.  To the Apus System then.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30cA_0019]">. . . .</Text>


</TextLibrary>
