<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_NAME1]">ED24</Text>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0000]">Lumina is in an information war with Quesada.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0001]">Lumina is in an information war with Quesada.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0002]">An information war?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0003]">Sounds strange.  What is an information war?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0004]">It is a shadow war really.  Neither side will make any official move against the other but both are seeking superiority through both ancient and modern secrets.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0005]">It is a shadow war really.  Neither side will make any official move against the other but both are seeking superiority through both ancient and modern secrets.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0006]">Huh.  Where&apos;s Sable?  He&apos;s usually the one to tell me this kind of stuff, not you.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0007]">Interesting.  How are you and I going to be involved in this?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0008]">Sable isn&apos;t the one you need for this task.  I, however, am relevent to this task because Lumina has asked that we find a way to encrypt databanks throughout Lumina space to protect the information from being gathered by Quesadan &quot;Seekers&quot;.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0009]">I am relevent to this task because Lumina has asked that we find a way to encrypt databanks throughout Lumina space to protect the information from being gathered by Quesadan &quot;Seekers&quot;.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0010]">So we&apos;ve been given coordinates and we are to simply fly to these locations and encrypt the data before anyone gets to it?  Sounds easy.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0011]">So we&apos;ve been given coordinates and we are to simply fly to these locations and encrypt the data before anyone gets to it?  Sounds easy.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0012]">Indeed, it will require only a minority of my processing cycles to complete.  However, Quesadan ships are already searching for this data.  If we run into any, we are contractually obligated to eliminate them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0013]">Indeed, it will require only a minority of my processing cycles to complete.  However, Quesadan ships are already searching for this data.  If we run into any, we are contractually obligated to eliminate them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0014]">Just leave that to me then.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0015]">The Quesadans have helped us in the past.  I don&apos;t like the idea of attacking them now.  On the other hand, they are invading Lumina&apos;s territory so I suppose it is only fair.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0016]">We will need to report back to Lumina&apos;s Ministry of Technology to receive our reward when we&apos;ve finished.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q33aB_0017]">Your moral logic is unintersting to me, but it is factually correct that Lumina is implying hositilites by seeking private information in Lumina space.  We will need to report back to Lumina&apos;s Ministry of Technology to receive our reward when we&apos;ve finished.</Text>
</TextLibrary>
