<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_NAME1]">SABLE</Text>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0000]">So, what did the Degani ask us to do?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0001]">It is suprising they asked for you, and not the senior member of our crew.  So, what did the Degani ask us to do?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0002]">They told me, for a change, that a pirate has been robbing ships of food with the threat of surrounding them with mines and leaving them to rot.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0003]">They told me that a pirate has been robbing ships of food with the threat of surrounding them with mines and leaving them to rot.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0004]">Interesting, so he has been stealing food but not money, and allowing his victims to live afterward.  That&apos;s unusual.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0005]">Interesting, so he has been stealing food but not money, and allowing his victims to live afterward.  That&apos;s unusual.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0006]">I doubt he will be much of a threat to us, since he mostly relies of minelaying equipment.  I mean, c&apos;mon, how many times have we looked at our enemy&apos;s equipment and said, &quot; Oh no! Not a minelayer!&quot;</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0007]">I find it more interesting that you assume it is a &quot;he&quot; and not a &quot;she&quot;.  A woman could be just as capable a pirate as a man.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0008]">That&apos;s. . . a strangely accurate point.  How do we find him?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0009]">I only assumed so because I attributed the theft of food to gluttony.  And, hmm. . . that doesn&apos;t really explain much, does it?  Fine, it is a she.  Where can we find her?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0010]">We are to collect a bunch of delicacies from around the galaxy.  It will be expensive, but the payoff should be worth it.  The first item on our list is in this very system on Degani VII.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q34aB_0011]">We are to collect a bunch of delicacies from around the galaxy.  It will be expensive, but the payoff should be worth it.  The first item on our list is in this very system on Degani VII.</Text>

</TextLibrary>
