<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_NAME1]">Sable</Text>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0000]">So the contact I met with is associated with a branch of the MRI led by the eccentric billionaire Nasty Butler.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0001]">So the contact I met with is associated with a branch of the MRI led by the eccentric billionaire Nasty Butler.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0002]">Nasty Butler?  I assume there is some kind of story behind that name, right?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0003]">Nasty Butler?  I assume there is some kind of story behind that name, right?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0004]">No.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0005]">No.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0006]">. . . .</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0007]">. . . .</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0008]">Anyway, he wants us to test out some strange Psionic Weaponry they&apos;ve developed.  It&apos;s useable only by telepaths, hence why he met with me.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0009]">Anyway, he wants us to test out some strange Psionic Weaponry they&apos;ve developed.  It&apos;s useable only by telepaths, hence why he met with me.  Well, that and you smell bad.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0010]">Let me guess, he&apos;s not just going to hand over their newly developed weaponry for free, is he?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0011]">I'm going to pretend I didn't hear that.  Let me guess, he&apos;s not just going to hand over their newly developed weaponry for free, is he?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0012]">I don&apos;t know the price, but I do know they want us to prove ourselves.  They&apos;ve allowed a certain Pirate Steve to escape from his detention cell on Serpens III and they want us to take him out to prove our combat skills.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0013]">I don&apos;t know the price, but I do know they want us to prove ourselves.  They&apos;ve allowed a certain Pirate Steve to escape from his detention cell on Serpens III and they want us to take him out to prove our combat skills.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0014]">A single pirate escaped into space, and all we&apos;re given to find him is the name Steve?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0015]">A single pirate escaped into space, and all we&apos;re given to find him is the name Steve?  What kind of name is Steve, anyway?  I mean. . Steve?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0016]">Actually, he&apos;s been tagged with a tracking beacon and I&apos;ve already had ED load his coordinates into our navigation computer.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q300Aa_0017]">Hey!  My father was named Steve.  It happens to be a royal name dating back to the King of Corneria!  Anyway, this pirate was tagged with a tracking beacon.  He'll be no trouble to locate.</Text>


</TextLibrary>
