<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_NAME1]">Sable</Text>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0000]">I was told Nasty Butler approved of how we handled the selected Pirate.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0001]">I was told Nasty Butler approved of how we handled the selected Pirate.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0002]">That&apos;s good to hear, but is that all the demonstration he needs to trust us with prototype technology?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0003]">We? Hardly.  I manned the guns AND piloted the ship while you sat in the back, meditating!</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0004]">Your intutition is correct, that is not all he will require of us.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0005]">Perhaps that was what it looked like to you.  In truth I was practicing the ancient technique of Battle Meditation, subtly influencing the entire outcome of the battle.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0006]">Alright, what&apos;s next on the agenda then?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0007]">I heard you snoring. . .</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0008]">It would seem we have been asked to gather 20 tons of Alloys as a proof that we are capable of obtaining needed resources.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0009]">Hmm, that is compelling evidence against me.  Would you believe I was DREAMING of using Battle Meditation?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0010]">Does he actually NEED these Alloys for anything?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0011]">I don&apos;t buy that.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0012]">I was told he is going to melt them down and have them used to form a statue of a penguin, but they could just be trying to mess with my head.  The MRI have been known to do that, being telepaths.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0013]">Alright, would you believe I was dreaming about turtles?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0014]">You have got to be kidding me.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0015]">That&apos;ll do.  Back onto the matter at hand, what is it that Mr. Butler has in mind for us now?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0016]">I wish I was.  Anyway, we are to deliver these to his home on Serpens III once we have them.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0017]">He wants us to gather 20 Alloys, probably via mining, and deliver them to his home on Serpens III.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0018]">Alright, let&apos;s get going then.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30bA_0019]">Alright, let&apos;s get moving.</Text>


</TextLibrary>
