<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<TextLibrary>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_NAME1]">Lydia</Text>

   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0000]">Well, Sable&apos;s little attunement is going to require a little work on my part.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0001]">Well, Sable&apos;s little attunement is going to require a little work on my part.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0002]">Attunement?  I thought we were getting a weapon?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0003]">Attunement?  I thought we were getting a weapon?  Has he been telling you more than me?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0004]">We actually already have what they&apos;re giving us.  It won&apos;t do us any good until we&apos;ve got our telepath bound to it though.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0005]">We actually already have what they&apos;re giving us.  It won&apos;t do us any good until we&apos;ve got our telepath bound to it though.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0006]">I&apos;m not sure I understand.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0007]">I&apos;m not sure I understand.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0008]">The prototype technology was the Cobalt Magnifier and we have that already, kid.  Once bound to a particular telepath, it will allow us to use all that psionic energy we come across as a fuel for special weapons.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0009]">The prototype technology was the Cobalt Magnifier and we have that already.  Once bound to a particular telepath, it will allow us to use all that psionic energy we come across as a fuel for special weapons.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0010]">Alright, what is it that you need to do then?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0011]">Well what role are you supposed to be playing in all of this?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0012]">I&apos;m supposed to get a hold of some refined crystals with a high level of Cobalt Flux.  They&apos;ll somehow be used in the attunement.  I don&apos;t know how that works, but I DO have experience with refining crystals.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0013]">I&apos;m supposed to get a hold of some refined crystals with a high level of Cobalt Flux.  They&apos;ll somehow be used in the attunement.  I don&apos;t know how that works, but I DO have experience with refining crystals.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0014]">All we need is for me to go gather the raw crystal right?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0015]">Let me guess, you&apos;re going to let me do all the mining and you&apos;ll sit back and look the crystal over once I&apos;m done?</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0016]">You got it, kid.  Mine me up 30 tons of Crystal.  With that much I should be able to get what we need if we take it to my workstation back in Erebus.</Text>
   <Text tag="[Conv_Q30fA_0017]">Yep, that&apos;s more or less how things are going to fly with me.  Be sure not to stop until you&apos;ve got 30 tons of the crystals at my workstation in Erebus.</Text>
</TextLibrary>
